{"qid": "0", "question": "Do you know who the authors of \"preinfarction blood pressure and smoking are determinants for a fatal outcome of myocardial infarction a prospective analysis from the finnmark study\" are?", "answer": "Inger Nj\u00f8lstad, Egil Arnesen"}
{"qid": "1", "question": "Do you know who the authors of \"subtle and underrecognized side effects of neuroleptic treatment in children with tourette s disorder\" are?", "answer": "Bruun Rd"}
{"qid": "2", "question": "Do you know who the authors of \"isotype profile and clinical relevance of anticardiolipin antibodies in sjogren s syndrome\" are?", "answer": "Luft S, Jedryka-G\u00f3ral A, Ma. Khamashta, G. R. V. Hughes, D P D'Cruz, G. T. Swana, P. Jagiello, Ma\u0142dykowa H"}
{"qid": "3", "question": "Who wrote the \"bcr breakpoint and prognosis of chronic phase chronic myeloid leukemia letter comment\" paper?", "answer": "Ken I. Mills, Peter Benn, E MacKenzie, Birnie Gd"}
{"qid": "4", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"patterns and trends of newly diagnosed hiv infections among adults and adolescents in correctional and noncorrectional facilities united states 2008 2011?\" ", "answer": "Albert E. Barskey, Angela L. Hernandez, Aruna Surendera Babu, Lorena Espinoza"}
{"qid": "5", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"assessing the risk of breast cancer?\" ", "answer": "Caroline S. Rhoads, Joann G. Elmore, Suzanne W. Fletcher"}
{"qid": "6", "question": "Who wrote the \"levels of phosphorylated p70 s6 kinase and phosphorylated erk1 2 predict overall survival and time to first treatment in chronic lymphocytic leukaemia\" paper?", "answer": "Russell Patmore, Lynn Cawkwell, Gina L. Eagle, Pointon Jo, Paul C. Evans, Abbott Jody, David Allsup, James R. Bailey, Ria L Brathwaite, John Greenman"}
{"qid": "7", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the paper \"altitude pulmonary edema below 8 000 feet what are we missing?\"", "answer": "Lawrence Raymond"}
{"qid": "8", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the paper \"comparison of visual acuity measured with allen figures and snellen letters using the b vat ii monitor?\"", "answer": "Gregg T. Lueder, David Garibaldi"}
{"qid": "9", "question": "Who wrote the \"an open label prospective pilot clinical study of denosumab for severe hyperparathyroidism in patients with low bone mass undergoing dialysis\" paper?", "answer": "Chien-Liang Chen, Chih Yang Hsu, Jenn Huei Renn, Nai Ching Chen, Kang Ju Chou, Po Tsang Lee, Hua Chang Fang"}
{"qid": "10", "question": "Where is the paper \"electrode placement and electroconvulsive therapy a search for the chimera reply\" published?", "answer": "archives of general psychiatry"}
{"qid": "11", "question": "Where is the paper \"selecting rational therapies in the neurosciences\" published?", "answer": "stroke"}
{"qid": "12", "question": "Where has the \"total knee arthroplasty for the treatment of chronic hemophilic arthropathy\" been published?", "answer": "clinical orthopaedics and related research"}
{"qid": "13", "question": "In which publication can I find the \"anti xa activity and event risk in patients with direct factor xa inhibitors initiated early after stroke\"?", "answer": "circulation"}
{"qid": "14", "question": "In which publication can I find the \"new evidence for stroke prevention clinical applications\"?", "answer": "jama"}
{"qid": "15", "question": "In which publication can I find the \"surgery for intracranial meningiomas in the elderly a clinical radiological grading system as a predictor of outcome\"?", "answer": "journal of neurosurgery"}
{"qid": "16", "question": "Where was the \"damage to the nasopharyngeal mucosa induced by current levels of urban air pollution a field study in lambs\" paper released?", "answer": "european respiratory journal"}
{"qid": "17", "question": "In which publication can I find the \"lymphocytic bronchiolitis associated with hiv infection\"?", "answer": "chest"}
{"qid": "18", "question": "Where has the \"autologous blood transfusion\" been published?", "answer": "plastic and reconstructive surgery"}
{"qid": "19", "question": "Where was the \"sorbinil and limited joint mobility in diabetics\" paper released?", "answer": "jama"}
{"qid": "20", "question": "Who collaborates with author Stephan Kapral to write paper \"ultrasonographic findings of the axillary part of the brachial plexus\"?", "answer": "Walter Mauritz, Manfred Greher, Gerald Retzl"}
{"qid": "21", "question": "Who works with author Patience H. White on the composition of \"improving health care transition and longitudinal care for adolescents and young adults with hydrocephalus report from the hydrocephalus association transition summit\"?", "answer": "Mark G. Hamilton, Tessa van der Willigen, David L. Wood, Cathy C. Cartwright, Michael A. Williams"}
{"qid": "22", "question": "Who partners with author V Paar in writing the paper \"p648long term physical activity leads to a significant decrease of serum h fabp and increase of sst2 levels a prospective clinical trail\"?", "answer": "Ioana-Alexandra Campean, Brigitte Litschauer, Jeanette Strametz-Juranek, Michael Sponder, Michael Lichtenauer, Bernhard Wernly, Monika Fritzer-Szekeres, Uta C. Hoppe, M. Emich"}
{"qid": "23", "question": "Who works with author Peng Xu on the composition of \"ulinastatin improves pulmonary function in severe burn induced acute lung injury by attenuating inflammatory response\"?", "answer": "Xiu-Jun Fu, Yong Fang, Chuan Gu, Min Yao, Ying Wang, Wei-Rong Yu"}
{"qid": "24", "question": "Who works with author Jan Erik Varhaug on the composition of \"prognostic impact of egf receptor in papillary thyroid carcinoma\"?", "answer": "Lars A. Akslen, AO Myking, Helga B. Salvesen"}
{"qid": "25", "question": "Who co-authors the paper \"activation of estrogen receptor g protein coupled receptor 30 enhances cholesterol cholelithogenesis in female mice\" with Min Liu?", "answer": "Helen H. Wang, Christopher K. Arnatt, Ornella de Bari, Piero Portincasa, David Q.-H. Wang"}
{"qid": "26", "question": "Who co-authors the paper \"external physical stimulation of the human fetus during episodes of low heart rate variation\" with Gerard H. A. Visser?", "answer": "H.J. Zeelenberg, J. de Vries, G.S. Dawes"}
{"qid": "27", "question": "Who collaborates with author David M. Hough to write paper \"utilisation of artificial intelligence for the development of an eus convolutional neural network model trained to enhance the diagnosis of autoimmune pancreatitis\"?", "answer": "Suresh T. Chari, Barham K. Abu Dayyeh, Zaiyang Long, Shigao Chen, Randall K. Pearson, Vinay Chandrasekhara, Shounak Majumder, Cadman L. Leggett, Elizabeth Rajan, Bret T. Petersen, Ferga C. Gleeson, Neil B. Marya, Andrew C. Storm, Kristin C. Mara, Prasad G. Iyer, Tarek Sawas, Patrick D Powers, Santhi Swaroop Vege, Michael J. Levy"}
{"qid": "28", "question": "Who is teaming up with author Gilbert Lam for the creation of \"building resilience in at risk elementary school children a school based initiative led by pediatric residents in ottawa canada\"?", "answer": "Megan E. Harrison, Arielle Singer"}
{"qid": "29", "question": "Who collaborates with author Weifeng Yuan to write paper \"association between plasminogen activator inhibitor 1 675 4g 5g polymorphism and sepsis a meta analysis\"?", "answer": "Weifeng Li, Wenjie Huang, Li Li, Hongfeng Zhou, Wei-Zhi Nie"}
{"qid": "30", "question": "Who is the author of both \"ptu 045 smokers with inflammatory bowel disease have low nicotine dependence\" and \"intestinal luminal ph in inflammatory bowel disease possible determinants and implications for therapy with aminosalicylates and other drugs\"?", "answer": "David S. Rampton"}
{"qid": "31", "question": "Who is the author of both \"new technique for airway correction in neonates with severe pierre robin sequence\" and \"rotation advancement of the midface by distraction osteogenesis\"?", "answer": "Arlen D. Denny"}
{"qid": "32", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"syndromic congenital myelofibrosis associated with a loss of function variant in rbsn\" and paper \"blue cone monochromacy visual function and efficacy outcome measures for clinical trials\"?", "answer": "Svetlana A. Yatsenko"}
{"qid": "33", "question": "Who authored the papers \"a clinical prediction model for estimating the probability of malignancy of a solitary pulmonary nodule in the philippine setting\" and \"clinical indicators of smear positive pulmonary tuberculosis among hospitalized patients\"?", "answer": "Albert L. Rafanan"}
{"qid": "34", "question": "Who authored the papers \"perceived versus measured functional vaginal capacity in cancer patients with sexual function concerns\" and \"phase ii study of intraperitoneal submicron particle paclitaxel spp plus iv carboplatin and paclitaxel in patients with epithelial ovarian cancer undergoing cytoreductive surgery\"?", "answer": "S.D. Yamada"}
{"qid": "35", "question": "Who is the author of both \"double arterial cannulation strategy for acute type a aortic dissection repair a 10 year single institution experience\" and \"effect of different surgical type of coronary artery bypass grafting on kidney injury a propensity score analysis\"?", "answer": "Feng-Chun Tsai"}
{"qid": "36", "question": "Who is the author of both \"the oxidative contribution of eight repeat bouts of high intensity interval training 3748 board 65 may 30 8 00 am 9 30 am\" and \"comparison of different methods used to assess body composition in college aged athletes 3352 board 40 june 1 8 00 am 9 30 am\"?", "answer": "Colin Shaw"}
{"qid": "37", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"impact of mode of delivery on pregnancy outcomes in women with premature rupture of membranes after 28 weeks of gestation in a low resource setting a prospective cohort study\" and paper \"reliability and validity of reflection exercises for obstetrics and gynecology residents\"?", "answer": "Amy M. Autry"}
{"qid": "38", "question": "Who penned the papers \"folliculitis decalvans microbiological signature is specific for disease clinical phenotype\" and \"lung microbiota and streptococcal enrichment in central lung cancer\"?", "answer": "Manuel Ponce-Alonso"}
{"qid": "39", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"breakthrough bleeding in hemophilia a patients on prophylaxis\" and paper \"children s hospital acquired thrombosis database chat a multi institutional database for prospective identification of independent risk factors\"?", "answer": "Natalie Laing Smith"}
{"qid": "40", "question": "Who is the most frequent collaborator of the writer Shang Hong-cai?", "answer": "Wang Jiaying"}
{"qid": "41", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Majd Tarabichi? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "Javad Parvizi"}
{"qid": "42", "question": "Who is the most frequent collaborator of the writer Soumojit Ghosh?", "answer": "Kamran Qureshi"}
{"qid": "43", "question": "Who is the most frequent collaborator of the writer Aroldo Rizzo?", "answer": "Francesco Ciccia"}
{"qid": "44", "question": "Who has worked with this author J. Macfie most often as a collaborator?", "answer": "M. Gatt"}
{"qid": "45", "question": "In terms of frequency of collaboration, who is the top collaborator with Jan Safvenberg?", "answer": "Gunnar Hillerdal"}
{"qid": "46", "question": "In terms of frequency of collaboration, who is the top collaborator with Hyeon Hoe Kim?", "answer": "Cheol Kwak"}
{"qid": "47", "question": "Who has worked with this author Jane Nixon most often as a collaborator?", "answer": "Julia Brown"}
{"qid": "48", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Lucius F. Wright? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "S. Lane Bicknell"}
{"qid": "49", "question": "Who has worked with this author Dominique Figarella-Branger most often as a collaborator?", "answer": "Henry Dufour"}
{"qid": "50", "question": "In 1986, how many individuals collaborated with author Arnoud van der Laarse", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "51", "question": "Takao Kogame collaborated with how many people in 1989", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "52", "question": "Adriana Belo collaborated with how many people in 2018", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "53", "question": "What is the count of collaborators with author Didier Meulendijks in 2013", "answer": "18"}
{"qid": "54", "question": "What is the count of collaborators with author Jeffery Segal in 2003", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "55", "question": "Richard J. Powell collaborated with how many people in 2020", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "56", "question": "How many collaborators does author Mehmet Yalchin have in 2015", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "57", "question": "In 2017, how many individuals collaborated with author Jonathan Hu", "answer": "9"}
{"qid": "58", "question": "Lukasz Hutnik collaborated with how many people in 2014", "answer": "33"}
{"qid": "59", "question": "What is the count of collaborators with author Albert F Schilte in 2001", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "60", "question": "How many papers did Ravindra Kumar Saran and Guy Helman write together?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "61", "question": "How many articles were jointly written by H.-T. Wu and Alexey Aleshin?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "62", "question": "How many articles were jointly written by Hee Chul Park and Woo Yong Lee?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "63", "question": "How many articles were jointly written by J. Hamill and R.E.A. van Emmerik?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "64", "question": "How many articles were jointly written by Techung Lee and John M. Canty?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "65", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers that Somashekhar V. Bellary and Michael J. Cassidy wrote jointly?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "66", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers that S. Schatz and Gunther H. Wiest wrote jointly?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "67", "question": "How many papers did Aziz Shaibani and Carlayne E. Jackson write together?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "68", "question": "What is the number of papers Ezio Bombardelli and Paolo Morazzoni co-authored?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "69", "question": "How many articles were jointly written by Camilla Loi and Michela Starace?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "70", "question": "Can you tell me how many articles quote \"treating mental health problems in health care workers they deserve a confidential service\"?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "71", "question": "Can you tell me how many articles quote \"insurance status and treatment candidacy of patients with hepatitis c taiwanese patients are luckier\"?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "72", "question": "How many research outputs reference the paper \"mortality of employees of the atomic weapons establishment 1951 82\"?", "answer": "15"}
{"qid": "73", "question": "What is the count of papers that reference \"intracuff pressures do not predict laryngopharyngeal discomfort after use of the laryngeal mask airway\"?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "74", "question": "What is the count of papers that reference \"a biopsy based 17 gene genomic prostate score as a predictor of metastases and prostate cancer death in surgically treated men with clinically localized disease\"?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "75", "question": "How many research outputs reference the paper \"acute responses to resistance training and safety\"?", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "76", "question": "Can you tell me how many articles quote \"safety of st john s wort hypericum perforatum\"?", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "77", "question": "What is the count of papers that reference \"long term clinical results with the ionescu shiley pericardial xenograft\"?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "78", "question": "How many research outputs reference the paper \"rupture of the liver associated with acute fatty liver of pregnancy\"?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "79", "question": "Can you tell me how many articles quote \"doomed to go in company with miserable pain surgical recognition and treatment of amputation related pain on the western front during world war 1\"?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "80", "question": "How many articles are cited in the paper \"has the twitching hour arrived for the ventilated patient\"?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "81", "question": "How many articles are cited in the paper \"prevalence of increased cardiac troponin i levels in patients with and without acute pulmonary embolism and relation of increased cardiac troponin i levels with in hospital mortality in patients with acute pulmonary embolism\"?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "82", "question": "Can you tell me the number of citations in the paper \"measurement inside the box\"?", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "83", "question": "How many papers does paper \"coronary anatomy as related to bicuspid aortic valve morphology\" cite?", "answer": "13"}
{"qid": "84", "question": "What is the number of papers the paper \"short course oral steroids alone for chronic rhinosinusitis\" cites?", "answer": "21"}
{"qid": "85", "question": "How many papers does paper \"depression induced by etretinate\" cite?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "86", "question": "How many papers does paper \"ischemia guided percutaneous coronary intervention for patients with stable coronary artery disease\" cite?", "answer": "40"}
{"qid": "87", "question": "How many papers does paper \"bilateral pleural effusions and right pneumothorax in a 25 year old man\" cite?", "answer": "9"}
{"qid": "88", "question": "What is the number of papers the paper \"hyperreactivity of blood leukocytes in patients with nafld to ex vivo lipopolysaccharide treatment is modulated by metformin and phosphatidylcholine but not by alpha ketoglutarate\" cites?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "89", "question": "Can you tell me the number of citations in the paper \"transfer for primary angioplasty the importance of time\"?", "answer": "26"}
{"qid": "90", "question": "Can you tell me the name of the paper by Amanda Katz that has been cited the most?", "answer": "patient derived xenografts for individualized care in advanced sarcoma"}
{"qid": "91", "question": "What is the most frequently cited paper from author CG Diamond?", "answer": "cystic adventitial degeneration of the popliteal artery ct demonstration and directed percutaneous therapy"}
{"qid": "92", "question": "What is the most frequently cited paper from author Rachid Jennane?", "answer": "fractal analysis of radiographic trabecular bone texture and bone mineral density two complementary parameters related to osteoporotic fractures"}
{"qid": "93", "question": "Can you tell me the name of the paper by Greet Ieven that has been cited the most?", "answer": "detecting pneumonia in patients with acute cough in primary results from the european grace study"}
{"qid": "94", "question": "Can you tell me the name of the paper by shaimaa seleem that has been cited the most?", "answer": "mo1236 early rebleeding and mortality in post hcv cirrhotic patients with esophageal variceal bleeding after band ligation predictive factors and value of vascular endothelial growth factor"}
{"qid": "95", "question": "Can you tell me the name of the paper by Jennifer Adrian that has been cited the most?", "answer": "clinical scale genome editing of the human bcl11a erythroid enhancer for treatment of the hemoglobinopathies"}
{"qid": "96", "question": "What is the most frequently cited paper from author L. Nneka Mobisson?", "answer": "knowledge attitudes and practices of healthcare providers towards prenatal hiv screening and prevention of mother to child transmission in nigeria"}
{"qid": "97", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author Ellen Laves?", "answer": "effects of social needs screening and in person service navigation on child health a randomized clinical trial"}
{"qid": "98", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author J. Randolph Hecht?", "answer": "abstract ct011 safety and efficacy results from a phase i dose escalation trial of the parp inhibitor talazoparib in combination with either temozolomide or irinotecan in patients with advanced malignancies"}
{"qid": "99", "question": "Can you tell me the name of the paper by Zsolt Papai-Szekely that has been cited the most?", "answer": "results of the phase iib part of time study evaluating tg4010 immunotherapy in stage iv non small cell lung cancer nsclc patients receiving first line chemotherapy"}
{"qid": "100", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers Hannah Lennon has authored?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "101", "question": "What is the number of papers written by author Sheri Lynn Ratoosh?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "102", "question": "How many papers did author Erica Jacobson write?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "103", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers Sang Heon Song has authored?", "answer": "9"}
{"qid": "104", "question": "How many scholarly papers has Natasha Keric authored?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "105", "question": "What is the number of papers written by author Syed Talha Ali Hamdani?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "106", "question": "Can you tell me the count of papers Thomas Lindow has authored?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "107", "question": "What is the number of papers written by author Diego F. Solano-Noguera?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "108", "question": "What is the number of papers written by author Ha-neul Seo?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "109", "question": "How many scholarly papers has Ueland K authored?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "110", "question": "In which venue were B Jeanrenaud and Fran\u00e7oise Rohner-Jeanrenaud most active in collaboration?", "answer": "international journal of obesity"}
{"qid": "111", "question": "Where did the majority of collaborations between Mario Luzi and Giovanni Antonini take place?", "answer": "american journal of cardiology"}
{"qid": "112", "question": "In which venue were Stephen Sazinsky and Jenny Shu most active in collaboration?", "answer": "cancer research"}
{"qid": "113", "question": "Where did K. Smudj and P. Nola collaborate the most?", "answer": "the lancet"}
{"qid": "114", "question": "Where did the majority of collaborations between R. Macy and A. A. Sucec take place?", "answer": "medicine and science in sports and exercise"}
{"qid": "115", "question": "Where did Per Bostr\u00f8m and Arne Westheim collaborate the most?", "answer": "journal of the american college of cardiology"}
{"qid": "116", "question": "Which venue did Andrew R. Mayrer and Lesley J. Crisp collaborate most?", "answer": "the journal of infectious diseases"}
{"qid": "117", "question": "Where did the majority of collaborations between Tilly A. Varughese and Sigal Yawetz take place?", "answer": "clinical infectious diseases"}
{"qid": "118", "question": "Which venue did Blaise Bossy and Ingo Diel collaborate most?", "answer": "clinical cancer research"}
{"qid": "119", "question": "Where did J Albin and Ali Shirkhoda collaborate the most?", "answer": "radiology"}
{"qid": "120", "question": "How many people does author Mary Fleming Knowles need to know at least to know author Samip Patel?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "121", "question": "For author Baiqin Qian to know author Jinwei Wang, what is the minimum number of people does he need to be acquainted with?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "122", "question": "For author L. Christine Ribeiro to know author Takanori Konishi, what is the minimum number of people does he need to be acquainted with?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "123", "question": "What is the minimum number of people that author Catherine de Sonnaville must know to get acquainted with author Esm\u00e9e J. Grobbee?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "124", "question": "For author Osamitsu Yagi to know author Naoki Miyao, what is the minimum number of people does he need to be acquainted with?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "125", "question": "How many people does author Lauren S. Blum need to know at least to know author S. A. Grover?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "126", "question": "How many people does author L. Irizarry need to know at least to know author E Cavallin-St\u00e5hl?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "127", "question": "What is the minimum number of people that author Yeon-Kyung Lee must know to get acquainted with author T.-H. Kim?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "128", "question": "For author G. Galov\u00e1 to know author A. Kunova, what is the minimum number of people does he need to be acquainted with?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "129", "question": "For author Kaori Yokochi to know author Bruna D. G. C. Moraes, what is the minimum number of people does he need to be acquainted with?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "130", "question": "For a reader of treatment of urinary incontinence after radical hysterectomy, which paper would you suggest from this list: a scalp cooling system designed to prevent chemotherapy induced alopecia our experience with implementation at a spanish public hospital, room b 10 17 2000 2 00 pm 4 00 pm ps thrombin cathepsin g and plasmin activity in plasma in cardiac surgical patients a 188, hypercalcemia and lymphadenopathy, sling operation for total incontinence following radical vulvectomy, researchers devise innovative method to overcome cancer related drug resistance, suprasellar meningiomas the effect of tumor location on postoperative visual outcome, a retrospective study analyzing the association between tumor response tr according to mcdonald criteria mc on mri and survival os in patients pts with glioblastoma gbm treated with antiangiogenic drugs ad, probability of female to male transmission of hiv 1 in thailand, tracing the use of torture electrically induced calcification of collagen in pig skin, frequency of prevalencevocal cord dysfunction among patients with uncontrolled asthma in vinnitsa region of ukraine? Please respond with the title, not the ID.", "answer": "sling operation for total incontinence following radical vulvectomy"}
{"qid": "131", "question": "If a person is interested in abstract 16413 results of treadmill stress testing need not be interpreted differently for predicting mortality in obese patients, which paper from the options the tyrosine kinase inhibitor tyrphostin ag126 reduces the development of colonic lieus in the mouse after surgical manipulation of the colon, an anatomical study of the lumbosacral plexus as related to the minimally invasive transpsoas approach to the lumbar spine, intensive antiplatelet therapy for reduction of ischaemic events, somatic bi allelic loss of tsc genes in eosinophilic solid and cystic renal cell carcinoma, comparative advantages of small and large dose metrizamide myelography, fitness fatness and mortality the fit henry ford exercise testing project, risk factors for recurrence of arterial ischemic stroke in childhood, blood transfusion in patients with acute coronary syndrome authors reply, determinants of happiness and quality of life in patients with rheumatoid arthritis a structural equation modelling approach, pd12 06 external validation of chokai score and comparison with stone score for the prediction of ureteral stones in japan a multicenter prospective observational study would you recommend? Note: Provide the full title of the suggested paper, not its ID.", "answer": "fitness fatness and mortality the fit henry ford exercise testing project"}
{"qid": "132", "question": "If a person is interested in abstract 2520 unprecedented renal responses to direct blockade of the renin angiotensin system with aliskiren a novel renin inhibitor, which paper from the options outcome from severe head injury in children and adolescents, the use of a long stem cemented femoral component in revision total hip replacement a follow up study of five to 16 years, role of two dimensional shear wave elastography in the assessment of chronic liver diseases, prognostic differences after ablation for atrial flutter compared to atrial fibrillation using a multistate transition model a nationwide cohort study, the development and efficacy of a pediatric cardiology fellowship online preparatory course, complete renin angiotensin aldosterone system raas blockade in high risk patients recent insights from renin blockade studies, natural history of asymptomatic patients with normally functioning or minimally dysfunctional bicuspid aortic valve in the community, adapting the dialysis unit to increased hematocrit levels, pretreatment proliferation parameters do not add to the predictive power of clinical factors in cervix cancer treated with definitive radiation therapy, o3 9 5randomized pii trial comparing cddp ts1 with cddp dtx with concurrent radiotherapy in locally advanced nsclc torg1018 would you recommend? Note: Provide the full title of the suggested paper, not its ID.", "answer": "complete renin angiotensin aldosterone system raas blockade in high risk patients recent insights from renin blockade studies"}
{"qid": "133", "question": "Consider a reader of good fat bad fat the increasingly complex interplay of adipose tissue and the cardiovascular system, which recommendation would you make from the following options: su1480 sleep duration and incident liver cancer in postmenopausal women, do clinicians know which of their patients have central venous catheters a multicenter observational study, obesity phenotypes diabetes and cardiovascular diseases, stuck on the trail of osteoclast differentiation, short term treatment with synchronized coronary venous retroperfusion before full reperfusion significantly reduces myocardial infarct size, coronary flow velocity changes after intravenous dipyridamole infusion measurements using intravascular doppler guide wire a documentation of flow inhomogeneity, impact of clinical pharmacists in inflammatory bowel disease centers during the covid 19 pandemic, accuracy of fat suppressed mr imaging of the shoulder for detection of partial thickness rotator cuff tears author s reply, atlas of pediatric orthopaedic surgery 4th edition, startle epilepsy a clinical study? Please remember to reply with the paper title instead of the ID.", "answer": "obesity phenotypes diabetes and cardiovascular diseases"}
{"qid": "134", "question": "Consider a reader of dietary fat intake and the risk of coronary heart disease in women, which recommendation would you make from the following options: is rivaroxaban safer and more effective than warfarin in patients with atrial fibrillation and stroke or tia author s reply, effects of acute high intensity exercise in normobaric hypoxia and hyperoxia on thoroughbred skeletal muscle 2066 board 218 june 2 2 00 pm 3 30 pm, abstract 12086 a novel approach to managing heart failure populations using actionable machine learning models, experience expertisecan simulation be used to tell the difference, a first case report of pulmonary hyalinizing granuloma associated with immunoglobulin a nephropathy, dietary fat at the heart of the matter, abstract 77 dietary acrylamide intake and the risk of head neck and thyroid cancer results from the netherlands cohort study, a study of the decision outcomes and financial costs of multidisciplinary team meetings mdms in oncology, prognosis in lung cancer physicians opinions compared with outcome and a predictive model, pulmonary sequestration an aberrant systemic blood supply demonstrated by computed tomographic angiography with 3 dimensional reconstruction? Please remember to reply with the paper title instead of the ID.", "answer": "dietary fat at the heart of the matter"}
{"qid": "135", "question": "If a person is interested in the swiss lithoclast a new device for intracorporeal lithotripsy, which paper from the options bacci a phase ii randomized double blind placebo controlled study of capecitabine bevacizumab plus atezolizumab versus capecitabine bevacizumab plus placebo in patients with refractory metastatic colorectal cancer, electrohydraulic lithotripsy of renal and ureteral calculi, diagnostic yield and clinical utility of sequencing familial hypercholesterolemia genes in patients with severe hypercholesterolemia, treatment of agitation in ad a randomized placebo controlled clinical trial, peripheral vascular diseases, patient controlled analgesia, abstract 890 effects of lewis lung carcinoma on trabecular microstructural changes in wild type and plasminogen activator inhibitor 1 deficient mice fed a high fat diet, nonbacterial thrombotic endocarditis in autologous bone marrow transplantation, decreased basal and postprandial plasma 5 hydroxytryptamine 5 ht in patients with functional dyspepsia fd a pilot study, correction effect of caffeine on neuromuscular function following eccentric based exercise would you recommend? Note: Provide the full title of the suggested paper, not its ID.", "answer": "electrohydraulic lithotripsy of renal and ureteral calculi"}
{"qid": "136", "question": "If a person is interested in orbital pseudotumor fine needle aspiration biopsy and response to therapy, which paper from the options development of a factor viii specific immunotherapy for hemophilia a, abstract 877 evolution of resistance to egfr inhibition from drug tolerant cancer cells, association between health belief and medication adherence in hypertensive patients, use of the hawkins hunter rocket wire in the biliary system, salivary gland tumors of the tongue analysis of 55 new cases and review of the literature, book review science has no sex the life of marie zakrzewska m d studies in social medicine by arleen marcia tuchman 336 pp illustrated chapel hill university of north carolina press 2006 34 95 0 8078 3020 8, are systemic corticosteroids useful in the management of orbital pseudotumors, chronic sinus node disease and coronary artery disease, loss of cxcr3 expression on memory b cells in individuals with long standing type 1 diabetes, long term mortality associated with acute kidney injury requiring dialysis would you recommend? Note: Provide the full title of the suggested paper, not its ID.", "answer": "are systemic corticosteroids useful in the management of orbital pseudotumors"}
{"qid": "137", "question": "For a reader of aerobilia and hypomotility of the sphincter of oddi in a patient with chronic intestinal pseudo obstruction, which paper would you suggest from this list: molecular sleuthing tracking ovarian cancer progression, the efficacy of tolterodine for prevention of catheter related bladder discomfort a prospective randomized placebo controlled double blind study, effect of jag2 on migration and invasion in colorectal cancer cell by praf2 independent of epithelial mesenchymal transition, predictive utility of prior positive urine culture of extended spectrum \u03b2 lactamase producing strains, stereotactic fractionated radiotherapy for chordomas and chondrosarcomas of the skull base, bs22 double positive cd86 mrc1 inflammatory macrophages in the pathogenesis of carotid atherosclerosis, re poor compliance with postvasectomy semen testing analysis of factors and barriers, p2612determinants of diagnostic delay in chronic thromboembolic pulmonary hypertension results from the international prospective cteph registry, analyzing the effects of alcohol on adolescent trauma using the national trauma data bank, frequencies and cyclical pattern of the human sphincter of oddi phasic activity? Please respond with the title, not the ID.", "answer": "frequencies and cyclical pattern of the human sphincter of oddi phasic activity"}
{"qid": "138", "question": "For a reader of bevacizumab a monoclonal antibody to the vascular endothelial growth factor vegf and irinotecan for treatment of recurrent primary malignant brain tumors in adults, which paper would you suggest from this list: prospective analysis of quality of life and survival following mesorectal excision for rectal cancer br j surg 2001 88 1617 22, residents work hours 3 multiple letters, book reviewthe chromosomes and their disorders an introduction for clinicians, distinctive cutaneous findings due to a rare complication from a warming device, bevacizumab a monoclonal antibody to vascular endothelial growth factor vegf and irinotecan for treatment of malignant gliomas, lb s t 11 social problem solving perceived stress and daily stressful events in chronic prostatitis, leiomyosarcoma in the right atrium and occluding the inferior vena cava, neurogenic claudication associated with posterior vertebral rim fractures in children, a phase ii trial of cabozantinib cabo for the treatment of radioiodine rai refractory differentiated thyroid carcinoma dtc in the first line setting, p1249 alcoholic liver disease and liver cancer as public health issues in the burden of liver related mortality in the last 15 years in brazil? Please respond with the title, not the ID.", "answer": "bevacizumab a monoclonal antibody to vascular endothelial growth factor vegf and irinotecan for treatment of malignant gliomas"}
{"qid": "139", "question": "If a person is interested in hysteroscopic resection of fibroid with thermal injury to sigmoid, which paper from the options heterotopic bone marrow formation in xenogeneic implants of insoluble bone matrix gelatin, tumor implantation in mouse humerus evokes movement related hyperalgesia exceeding that evoked by intramuscular carrageenan, asthmatic children parents knowledge is enough, impact of pectus excavatum on cardiopulmonary function, histopathological lung changes in children due to biomass fuel, endometrial ablation complicated by fatal hyponatremic encephalopathy, in vivo blockade of angiotensin ii receptors reduces the development of cell hypertrophy and if amplitude in spontaneously hypertensive rats, missed follow up is an independent predictor of survival in stage i lung cancer results from a large multi site academic institutional study, challenges and unfulfilled promises in parkinson s disease, a2 37 b cells regulate follicular helper t cells in healthy individuals and sjogren s patients but are defective in sle patients would you recommend? Note: Provide the full title of the suggested paper, not its ID.", "answer": "endometrial ablation complicated by fatal hyponatremic encephalopathy"}
